Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Aviation [includes one color photograph], 1929 - circa 1960s; 6 (Box 1538)
    - Verso: At Elgin Air Force Base, Nov. 1+2, 1956, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas in the back of a plane at Elgin Air Force Base], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas in an Air Force plane at Elgin Base], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting in an Air Force plane at the Elgin Base], 5
    - Note: [Letter from Pan American Public Relations] 8 September Dear Miss Davis: Sorry that you had to wait for these photographs of Mr. Thomas and Mr. Trippe, but our "boys" out at the airport in Photographic Department have been very busy. Hope you will stop by one of these days and we can reminisce! With best wishes. Sincerely, [signed] Althea Lister, 6
    - [left to right: unidentified man, Juan Trippe, Lowell Thomas] [3 copies], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and Juan Trippe] [4 copies], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas], 9
  - Subject files: Aviation Hall of Fame [color photographs], 1963; 7 (Box 1538)
    - [Lowell Thomas at the Aviation Hall of Fame], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and an unidentified man at the Aviation Hall of Fame] [2 copies], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man at the Aviation Hall of Fame], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and man at the Aviation Hall of Fame], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and man at the Aviation Hall of Fame], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with a man and woman at the Aviation Hall of Fame], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas speakign to an elderly man and woman], 7
  - Subject files: Awards, 1969 - 1970s; 8 (Box 1538)
    - [George Washington Award, circa 1970s], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man looking at a painting], 2
    - [The American Legion award for contributions to aviation, 1969], 3
    - Verso: Gen. Geo. Kinney, Col. Bernt Balchen, L.T., Harry Bruno, 3-verso
  - Subject files: Senator Howard Baker, 1981; 9 (Box 1538)
    - The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 1
    - Verso: The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 1-verso
    - The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 2
    - Verso: The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 2-verso
    - The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 3
    - Verso: The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 3-verso
    - The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 4
    - Verso: The 1981 IPA Daniel Webster Award, Presented to Senator Howard Baker by Lowell Thomas, on April 30th, 1981, in the Senate Reception Room in the Capitol, 4-verso
  - Subject files: McClelland Barclay [sketches], circa 1929 - 1930; 10 (Box 1538)
    - Note: Gen. Jimmy Doolittle by McClelland Barclay, 1
    - Gen. Jimmy Doolittle by McClelland Barclay [3 copies], 2
    - Verso: This photograph made by the studios of Hal Phyfe 50 West 56, New York City, 2-verso
    - Caption: To my friend & wonderful [?] "Doc" Jack [2 copies], 3
    - Verso: The jovial Dr. William Jack, former chief assistant to the great Sir William Osler. This photograph made by the studios of Hal Phyfe 50 West 56, New York City, 3-verso
    - Caption: To Dan Edwards, my friend the iron man, 4
    - Caption: In the Caribbean Aug 11, 1929 off Haiti, 5
    - Verso: McClelland Barclay, a portrait by the artist himself; This photograph made by the studios of Hal Phyfe 50 West 56, New York City, 5-verso
    - [Count Felix von Luckner, "The Sea Devil"], 6
    - The Sea Devil's brother, Count Ferdinand von Luckner, who was a member of the party, 7
    - Verso: The Sea Devil's brother, Count Ferdinand von Luckner, who was a member of the party, 7-verso
    - [Drawing of McClelland Barclay by Charliw The Bo'S'N], 8
  - Subject files: Tracy Bartholomew ("The House on the Hill" ), circa 1914; 11 (Box 1538)
    - Caption: "The House on the Hill", 1
    - Note: [Letter to Frances Ryan Thomas from Tracy Bartholomew], [PDF file], 2
  - Subject files: T. W. Beaumont, 1963; 12 (Box 1538)
    - T. W. Beaumont - T. E. Lawrence's [?] gunman in the Arabian Campaign. Taken for publicity. 1963., 1
    - Verso: T. W. Beaumont - T. E. Lawrence's [?] gunman in the Arabian Campaign. Taken for publicity. 1963., 1-verso
    - Note: The Brief mention of Lawrence of Arabia disappointed me. You see, I am one of the few left who actually served with him in the campaign [continued], 2
  - Subject files: Leon Blum, Premier of France, and Lowell Thomas, circa 1936 - 1938; 13 (Box 1538)
    - Lowell Thomas with Leon Blum, Premier of France, 1
    - Verso: ACME Newspictures, 32 Rue Le Peletier, Paris-9, Tel. Provence 35-25, 1-verso
  - Subjust files: Books, circa 1956, 1964; 14 (Box 1538)
    - [Seven Wonders of the World book signing, circa 1956], 1
    - [display for Lowell Thomas's book of the High Mountains, circa 1964] [3 copies], 2
  - Subject files: Bohemian Grove, circa 1946; 15 (Box 1538)
    - Cave man's 1946 Midsummer Encampment; Front row, seated, left to right: Lucius M. Boomer-Clarence Budington Kelland-Dr. George S. Johnson-Gen. H. L. George-Herbet Hoover-Dr. Ray Lyman Wilbur-Jeremiah Wilbank-Edgar Rickard; Back row, left to right: Allan Hoover-Dr. L. R. Chandler-Herbert Hoover. Jr.-___ ___Sawyer-R. Emerson Swart-Arthur A. Curtice-Charles K. Field-Alfred C. Mattei-Lowell Thomas-Walderman Johansen-Wm. I. Nichols-Fred G. Clark, 1
    - Verso: Cave man's 1946 Midsummer Encampment; Front row, seated, left to right: Lucius M. Boomer-Clarence Budington Kelland-Dr. George S. Johnson-Gen. H. L. George-Herbet Hoover-Dr. Ray Lyman Wilbur-Jeremiah Wilbank-Edgar Rickard; Back row, left to right: Allan Hoover-Dr. L. R. Chandler-Herbert Hoover. Jr.-___ ___Sawyer-R. Emerson Swart-Arthur A. Curtice-Charles K. Field-Alfred C. Mattei-Lowell Thomas-Walderman Johansen-Wm. I. Nichols-Fred G. Clark, 1-verso
    - HH Jr. [Herbert Hoover, Jr.], Lowell Thomas, C.K. Field, 2
    - Verso: HH Jr. [Herbert Hoover, Jr.], Lowell Thomas, C.K. Field, 2-verso
    - Bud Kelland, 3
    - Verso: Bud Kelland, 3-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, 4
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 4-verso
    - Lucius Boomer, Jeremiah Wilbank, 5
    - Verso: Lucius Boomer, Jeremiah Wilbank, 5-verso
    - E. Rickard, 6
    - Verso: E. Rickard, 6-verso
    - General George, 7
    - Verso: General George, 7-verso
    - HH [Herbert Hoover] speaking at The Circle to The Bohemian Grove, his annual talk, 8
    - Verso: HH [Herbert Hoover] speaking at The Circle to The Bohemian Grove, his annual talk, 8-verso
    - Grove Theatre and stage, where play [is] produced, 9
    - Verso: Grove Theatre and stage, where play [is] produced, 9-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Paul Smith, ?, 10
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Paul Smith, ?, 10-verso
    - Road, 11
    - Verso: Road, 11-verso
    - [Paul Smith], 12
    - Verso: [Paul Smith], 12-verso
    - Ray Lyman Wilbur, 13
    - Verso: Ray Lyman Wilbur, 13-verso
    - HH [Herbert Hoover], 14
    - Verso: HH [Herbert Hoover], 14-verso
    - Allan Hoover, 15
    - Verso: Allan Hoover, 15-verso
    - Lucius Boomer, 16
    - Verso: Lucius Boomer, 16-verso
    - Jeremiah Wilbank, 17
    - Verso: Jeremiah Wilbank, 17-verso
    - HH Jr. [Herbert Hoover, Jr.], 18
    - Verso: HH Jr. [Herbert Hoover, Jr.], 18-verso
    - HH [Herbert Hoover] and A.C. Mattei, 19
    - Verso: HH [Herbert Hoover] and A.C. Mattei, 19-verso
    - Loren R. Chandler, 20
    - Verso: Loren R. Chandler, 20-verso
    - Verso: Dec 20, 1946, 21
    - Verso: Dec 20, 1946, 21-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, center, Paul Smith at left], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group a Bohemian Grove], 23
    - [Five unidentified men eating outside at Bohemian Grove], 24
    - [Man laying on a mock sacrificial table], 25
    - [Unidentified man], 26
  - Subject files: Bohemian Club [includes color photographs], 1948 - 1981; 16 (Box 1538)
    - Note: Bohemian Grove - L.T. was non-resident member was from date 30's sponsored by Pres. Hoover. Monte Rio on Russian River, 1
    - l. to r. Haig Mardikian, General Hunter Harris, the Marco Polo of our time Lowell Thomas, Connie Mardikian and half of George Mardikian-at Omar Khayyam's September 23, 1976, 2
    - Verso: l. to r. Haig Mardikian, General Hunter Harris, the Marco Polo of our time Lowell Thomas, Connie Mardikian and half of George Mardikian-at Omar Khayyam's September 23, 1976, 2-verso
    - Bob Bonaparte, Bruce Cole, Walter Trohan, John "Dick" Tresevant, Jack [?], Glen Campbell, Monte Spaight, Andy Hoover, Henry Hearns, Pete Hoover, Gordon Hanna, John Cowles, Jack Howard, Bus Mosbacher, Chuck Rettenburg, Wally Sterling, Bob Swain, Haig Mard- [Mardikian], Bob O'Brien, L.T., John Sweringer, Geo. [?],Bob [?] Jr., Tom Sunderland, 3
    - Verso: Bob Bonaparte, Bruce Cole, Walter Trohan, John "Dick" Tresevant, Jack [?], Glen Campbell, Monte Spaight, Andy Hoover, Henry Hearns, Pete Hoover, Gordon Hanna, John Cowles, Jack Howard, Bus Mosbacher, Chuck Rettenburg, Wally Sterling, Bob Swain, Haig Mard- [Mardikian], Bob O'Brien, L.T., John Sweringer, Geo. [?],Bob [?] Jr., Tom Sunderland, 3-verso
    - Back row - Haig Mardikian, Bob Thomas, Jerry Hume, Phillip Beakman, Sandy Lankler, Bill Schiffers, Morley Thompson, Bob Bonapart, Boise Cascade, Bob O'Brien, Glen Campbell, Jack Frtiz, John Blair, Bob Smith, (Sun Oil Found.), Bruce Cole, Bob Swain. Front row: Jack Hume, Tom Sunderland, Tom Watson, Wally Sterling, L.T., Henry Kearns, Bob Swain, Jack Howard, 1981 (July), 4
    - Verso: Back row - Haig Mardikian, Bob Thomas, Jerry Hume, Phillip Beakman, Sandy Lankler, Bill Schiffers, Morley Thompson, Bob Bonapart, Boise Cascade, Bob O'Brien, Glen Campbell, Jack Frtiz, John Blair, Bob Smith, (Sun Oil Found.), Bruce Cole, Bob Swain. Front row: Jack Hume, Tom Sunderland, Tom Watson, Wally Sterling, L.T., Henry Kearns, Bob Swain, Jack Howard, 1981 (July), 4-verso
    - Row - back: Dan McMichael, 2. Glenn Campbell 3. Jack Howard 4. Monte Spaight 5. Bob O'Brien 6. Hack Miller 7. L.T. 8. Emil "Bus" Mosbacher 9. John Sweringen 10. Jack Dempsey. Middle row: Howard Wood, Jaqueline Hume, Wally Sterling, Geo. Russell, Bob Swaine-Capt., Geo. Mardikian, Sam Payne, Tom Sunderland, Henry Ford. Front: Dr. Richard Bobb, Michael Howard, H. Hoover (Pete) III, Haig Mard- [Mardikian], Bob Bonapart, 5
    - Verso: Row - back: Dan McMichael, 2. Glenn Campbell 3. Jack Howard 4. Monte Spaight 5. Bob O'Brien 6. Hack Miller 7. L.T. 8. Emil "Bus" Mosbacher 9. John Sweringen 10. Jack Dempsey. Middle row: Howard Wood, Jaqueline Hume, Wally Sterling, Geo. Russell, Bob Swaine-Capt., Geo. Mardikian, Sam Payne, Tom Sunderland, Henry Ford. Front: Dr. Richard Bobb, Michael Howard, H. Hoover (Pete) III, Haig Mard- [Mardikian], Bob Bonapart, 5-verso
    - Gov. [Governor] + Mrs. Pyle of Arizona + 2 daughters, Mr. + Mrs. Mardikian [circa 1950s], 6
    - Verso: Gov. [Governor] + Mrs. Pyle of Arizona + 2 daughters, Mr. + Mrs. Mardikian [circa 1950s], 6-verso
    - Former Gov. [Governor] of Arizona, Howard Pyle and wife and 2 daughters; Geo. Mardikian [at right] [circa 1950s], 7
    - Verso: Former Gov. [Governor] of Arizona, Howard Pyle and wife and 2 daughters; Geo. Mardikian [at right] [circa 1950s], 7-verso
    - Cave Man Camp; 1948 Grove Encampment; Sitting (left to right) Dr. Robert Swain, Jeremiah Milbank, Edgar Rickard, Lowell Thomas, Ray Vir Den, Paul Smith, THE CHIEF [Herbert Hoover], Richard C. Hunt, Dr. R. L. Wilbur, Dr. Julius Klein, Clarence Bud Kelland, Allan Hoover. Standing (left to right), A. C. Mattei, A. W. Peake, John J. McCloy, Dr. L. R. Chandler, General Mark W. Clark, Herbert Hoover, Jr., Dr. George S. Johnson, Henry J. Taylor, Sidney A. Mitchell, 8
    - Verso: Cave Man Camp; 1948 Grove Encampment; Sitting (left to right) Dr. Robert Swain, Jeremiah Milbank, Edgar Rickard, Lowell Thomas, Ray Vir Den, Paul Smith, THE CHIEF [Herbert Hoover], Richard C. Hunt, Dr. R. L. Wilbur, Dr. Julius Klein, Clarence Bud Kelland, Allan Hoover. Standing (left to right), A. C. Mattei, A. W. Peake, John J. McCloy, Dr. L. R. Chandler, General Mark W. Clark, Herbert Hoover, Jr., Dr. George S. Johnson, Henry J. Taylor, Sidney A. Mitchell, 8-verso
    - Mr. Robert Swain, 9
    - Verso: Mr. Robert Swain, 9-verso
    - L to R [left to right] Grimm, P, T D.A Brophy, L.T., 10
    - Verso: L to R [left to right] Grimm, P, T D.A Brophy, L.T., 10-verso
    - Left to right - Buddy Rogers, husband of Mary Pickford, L.T. and Geo. Killian, 11
    - Verso: Left to right - Buddy Rogers, husband of Mary Pickford, L.T. and Geo. Killian, 11-verso
    - L.T. and George Killian Chairman of the Board of [?] and the American Presidents Steamship Co., 12
    - Verso: L.T. and George Killian Chairman of the Board of [?] and the American Presidents Steamship Co., 12-verso
    - August 21, 1962, Here's another pictures from the Bohemian Grove of me draining the last drop of a glass of vodka. I suppose it might as well be put with our biographical file, but I don't know why!!, 13
    - Note: August 21, 1962, Here's another pictures from the Bohemian Grove of me draining the last drop of a glass of vodka. I suppose it might as well be put with our biographical file, but I don't know why!!, 14
    - Members and Guests of Caveman's, Saturday, July 29, 1950; Sitting (from left to right) Guy George Gabrielson-A.C. Mattei-Lowell Thomas-THE CHIEF [Herbert Hoover]-Clarence Budington Kelland-Jeremiah Milbank-Fred G. Clark. Standing (from left to right) Dr. George S. Johnson-James Kerney, Jr.-Herbert Hoover Jr.-Peter Grimm-Richard Wilson-A. W. Peake-Dr. L. R. Chandler-Allan Hoover-Edgar Rickard-Raymond Moley Compliments of: Edgar Rickard, Stanford University Hospital, Clay & Webster Sts., San Francisco 15, Calif., 15
    - Verso: Members and Guests of Caveman's, Saturday, July 29, 1950; Sitting (from left to right) Guy George Gabrielson-A.C. Mattei-Lowell Thomas-THE CHIEF [Herbert Hoover]-Clarence Budington Kelland-Jeremiah Milbank-Fred G. Clark. Standing (from left to right) Dr. George S. Johnson-James Kerney, Jr.-Herbert Hoover Jr.-Peter Grimm-Richard Wilson-A. W. Peake-Dr. L. R. Chandler-Allan Hoover-Edgar Rickard-Raymond Moley Compliments of: Edgar Rickard, Stanford University Hospital, Clay & Webster Sts., San Francisco 15, Calif., 15-verso
    - Members and Guests of Caveman's, Saturday, July 29, 1950; Sitting (from left to right) Guy George Gabrielson-A.C. Mattei-Lowell Thomas-THE CHIEF [Herbert Hoover]-Clarence Budington Kelland-Jeremiah Milbank-Fred G. Clark. Standing (from left to right) Dr. George S. Johnson-James Kerney, Jr.-Herbert Hoover Jr.-Peter Grimm-Richard Wilson-A. W. Peake-Dr. L. R. Chandler-Allan Hoover-Edgar Rickard-Raymond Moley Compliments of: Edgar Rickard, Stanford University Hospital, Clay & Webster Sts., San Francisco 15, Calif., 16
    - Sir Edmund Hillary and LT at The Grove, 17
    - Verso: Sir Edmund Hillary and LT at The Grove, 17-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to the sign for "Sons of Preachers Night Campfire Show"], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and two unidentified men at The Grove], 19
    - [Band on the banks of a pond at The Grove], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas and a group of men at The Grove], 21
    - [Pond at The Grove], 22
    - [Posters for shows at The Grove], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas and two mwn at The Grove], 24
  - Subject files: Bohemian Club [includes color photographs], 1948 - 1981; 17 (Box 1538)
    - [Herbert Hoover], 1
    - [left to right: Richard M. Nixon, unidentified man, Herbert Hoover], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men at the Boheniam Club], 3
    - [Outdoor dinner tables at the Bohemian Club], 4
    - [Lake at the Bohemian Club], 5
    - [A show being put on at the Bohemian Club], 6
    - [Orchestra on the banks of a pond at the Bohemian Club], 7
    - [Unidentified man next to a pond at the Bohemian Club], 8
    - [Large trees at the Bohemian Club], 9
    - [Forest in the Bohemian Club], 10
    - [Sign for a tree named after Herbert Hoover at the Bohemian Club], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and a group at the Bohemian Club], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of men at the Bohemian Club], 13
    - [Members (?) of the Bohemian Club], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group at the Bohemian Club], 15
  Box 1539
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Bohemian Club, circa 1950s; 1 (Box 1539)
    - Belongs to Fred Clark., L.T. + Sec'y for air Jas. Douglas [James H. Douglas, Jr., United States Secretary of the Air Force]; 8x10 for Cap. [Capital] Cities, 1
    - Verso: Belongs to Fred Clark., L.T. + Sec'y for air Jas. Douglas [James H. Douglas, Jr., United States Secretary of the Air Force]; 8x10 for Cap. [Capital] Cities, 1-verso
    - [Herbert Hoover], 2
    - [Herbert Hoover], 3
    - [Herbert Hoover at left, Lowell Thomas, center], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas], 7
    - [Unidentified man at the Bohemian Club], 8
    - [Man at the Bohemian Club], 9
    - [Member (?) at the Bohemian Club], 10
    - [Unidentified man at the Bohemian Club], 11
    - [Unidentified man at the Bohemian Club], 12
    - [Man having a meal at the Bohemian Club], 13
    - [Herbert Hoover at right], 14
    - [Herbert Hoover at left, Lowell Thomas, center], 15
  - Subject files: Bohemian Club [color photographs], circa 1961; 2 (Box 1539)
    - Bohemian, 1961, 1
    - Note: Bohemian, 1961, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas on the buffet line at the Bohemian Club], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man eating appetizers at the Bohemian Club], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and other members of the Bohemain Club], 5
  - Subject files: Bohemian Club [color photographs], circa 1970s; 3 (Box 1539)
    - [Lowell Thomas and friends chatting at a table at the Bohemian Club ], 1
    - [Man tying his shoe], 2
  - Subject files: Bohemian Club, undated; 4 (Box 1539)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Herbert Hoover and others seated at table], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Bohemian Club members eating a meal], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with other members of the Bohemian Club], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Large campfire at the Bohemian Club], 6
    - [People watching the orchestra at the Bohemian Club], 7
    - [Unidentified man in the forest at the Bohemian Club], 8
    - [Outdoor feast at the Bohemian Club], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas, Herbert Hoover and others seated at table], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas], 12
    - [People eating at the Bohemian Club], 13
    - [Three ladies sitting by a window], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas], 15
    - [People gathered at the Bohemian Club], 16
  - Subject files: Boulder Dam project [Hoover Dam], 1933 - 1934s; 5 (Box 1539)
    - [Hoover Dam construction], 1
    - [The construction of Hoover Dam], 2
    - [Hoover Dam], 3
    - [Three trucks full of people at Hoover Dam], 4
    - [Three men standing on a rock at the Hoover Dam], 5
    - [Man in a wooden lift during construction of the Hoover Dam], 6
    - [Man on a bulldozer (?) working on the Hoover Dam], 7
    - [Four construction workers at the Hoover Dam], 8
    - [Base camp for construction workers on the Hoover Dam], 9
    - [Children sitting outside of a house in Nevada (?)], 10
    - [Tunnels by the Hoover Dam], 11
    - [Man standing in tunnel at the Hoover Dam], 12
    - [Three men in an underground tunnel working on the Hoover Dam], 13
    - [Construction workers at the Hoover Dam], 14
    - [Man standing in the mouth of a tunnel at Hoover Dam], 15
    - [Two men sitting on boxes containing some type of powder at the Hoover Dam], 16
    - [Construction on the Hoover Dam], 17
    - [Dump truck at the Hoover Dam], 18
    - [Group of men working on the Hoover Dam], 19
    - [Construction at the Hoover Dam], 20
    - [Train delivering construction materials for the Hoover Dam], 21
    - [Group of men standing by sign for the "Boulder Canyon Project", also known as the future site of the Hoover Dam], 22
    - [Constructing the Hoover Dam], 23
    - [Construction workers working on the Hoover Dam], 24
    - [The Hoover Dam in its preliminary stages], 25
    - [Hoover Dam in progress of being built], 26
    - [Large wooden trailer used during construction of the Hoover Dam], 27
    - [Aerial view of the Hoover Dam construction], 28
    - [Hoover Dam construction lit up at night], 29
    - [The Hoover Dam], 30
  - Subject files: Marty Brill, circa 1936; 6 (Box 1539)
    - Marty Brill, 1
    - Note: envelope from Marty Brill to Lowell Thomas, 2
  - Subject files: Prosper Buranelli, undated; 7 (Box 1539)
    - Left to right, Louis Sherwin-radio news editor for LT, LT, Prosper Buranelli-radio news editor for LT, 1
    - Verso: Left to right, Louis Sherwin-radio news editor for LT, LT, Prosper Buranelli-radio news editor for LT, 1-verso
    - [left to right: Dan Edwards, Prosper Buranelli, unidentified man], 2
    - [left to right: Dan Edwards, Prosper Buranelli, unidentified man], 3
    - [Prosper Buranelli], 4
    - [Prosper Buranelli], 5
  - Subject files: Capital Cities [includes color photographs], undated; 8 (Box 1539)
    - Painting of Marco Polo reporting to Kubla Khan in Far Cathay. Painted by famed artist Marco Larrinaga. [?] L.T.'s broadcasting studio, 1
    - Verso: Painting of Marco Polo reporting to Kubla Khan in Far Cathay. Painted by famed artist Marco Larrinaga. [?] L.T.'s broadcasting studio, 1-verso
    - Note: Photo's taken in LT's Capital Cities office; painting of Marco Polo reporting to Kubla Khan, 2
    - Photo's taken in LT's Capital Cities office; painting of Marco Polo reporting to Kubla Khan [2 copies], 3
    - Photo's taken in LT's Capital Cities office; painting of Marco Polo reporting to Kubla Khan, 4
    - Photo's taken in LT's Capital Cities office; painting of Marco Polo reporting to Kubla Khan, 5
    - Photo's taken in LT's Capital Cities office; painting of Marco Polo reporting to Kubla Khan [3 copies], 6
    - Left to Right: Mr. James Righter, Publisher, Buffalo Evening news; Mr. C. Robert Thompson, V. Pres, WBEN-Inc.-"retired" manager WBEN-AM-FM-TV; Mr. Les Arries, Jr., V.P. and General Manager, WBEN-TV-AM; L.T. Robert J. Koch, Commercial Photographer, 193 E. Morris Ave., Buffalo 14, N.Y., 7
    - Verso: Left to Right: Mr. James Righter, Publisher, Buffalo Evening news; Mr. C. Robert Thompson, V. Pres, WBEN-Inc.-"retired" manager WBEN-AM-FM-TV; Mr. Les Arries, Jr., V.P. and General Manager, WBEN-TV-AM; L.T. Robert J. Koch, Commercial Photographer, 193 E. Morris Ave., Buffalo 14, N.Y., 7-verso
    - Note: Ray Shafer (middle) Gov. [Governor] of PA [Pennsylvania], Yale, [Lowell Thomas at right], 8
    - Dick Swain, (Pittsburgh), Ray Shafer, Gov. of PA, + L.T., 9
    - Verso: Dick Swain, (Pittsburgh), Ray Shafer, Gov. of PA, + L.T., 9-verso
    - [Dick Swain, Ray Shafer and Lowell Thomas], 10
    - [Dick Swain, Ray Shafer and Lowell Thomas], 11
    - [Governor Ray Shafer and Lowell Thomas], 12
    - [left to right: Francis Joseph Spellman, Cardinal Archbishop of New York, Lowell Thomas, unidentified man], 13
    - 3rd floor Capital Cities; Spellman [Francis Joseph Spellman, Cardinal Archbishop of New York] and Tom Murphy, 14
    - Note: 3rd floor Capital Cities; Spellman [Francis Joseph Spellman, Cardinal Archbishop of New York] and Tom Murphy, 15
    - [Francis Joseph Spellman, Cardinal Archbishop of New York and Lowell Thomas], 16
    - [Francis Joseph Spellman, Cardinal Archbishop of New York and Lowell Thomas], 17